[
    {
        "Question":
		{
			"question": "Q 1 - Which of the following is correct about C#?",
			"answerA": "A - It is component oriented.",
			"answerB": "B - It can be compiled on a variety of computer platforms.",
			"answerC": "C - It is a part of .Net Framework.",
			"answerD": "D - All of the above.",
			"correctAnswer": "D - All of the above."
		}
    },
    {
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 2 - Which of the following converts a type to \n a single Unicode character, where possible in C#?",
			"answerA": "A - ToSingle",
			"answerB": "B - ToByte",
			"answerC": "C - ToChar",
			"answerD": "D - ToDateTime",
			"correctAnswer": "C - ToChar"
		}
    },
    {
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 3 - Which of the following converts a type to a specified type in C#?",
			"answerA": "A - ToType",
			"answerB": "B - ToSbyte",
			"answerC": "C - ToSingle",
			"answerD": "D - ToString",
			"correctAnswer": "A - ToType"
		}
    },
    {
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 4 - Which of the following converts a type to an unsigned int type in C#?",
			"answerA": "A - ToType",
			"answerB": "B - ToUInt16",
			"answerC": "C - ToString",
			"answerD": "D - ToSingle",
			"correctAnswer": "B - ToUInt16"
		}
    },
    {
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 5 - Which of the following is the default access specifier of a class?",
			"answerA": "A - Internal",
			"answerB": "B - Private",
			"answerC": "C - Public",
			"answerD": "D - Protected",
			"correctAnswer": "A - Internal"
		}
    },
    {
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 6 - Which of the following preprocessor directive allows \n you to undefine a symbol in C#?",
			"answerA": "A - define",
			"answerB": "B - undef",
			"answerC": "C - region",
			"answerD": "D - endregion",
			"correctAnswer": "B - undef"
		}
    },
    {
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 7 - What will be the output of the following code? \n\n int i = 5, j; \n Console.WriteLine(j=int*2)",
			"answerA": "A - 0",
			"answerB": "B - 10",
			"answerC": "C - RunTime error",
			"answerD": "D - Compile-time error",
			"correctAnswer": "B - 10"
		}
    },
    {
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 8 - Which of the following keyword is used to declare a variable \n whose type will be automatically determined by the compiler?",
			"answerA": "A - This",
			"answerB": "B - Dynamic",
			"answerC": "C - Var",
			"answerD": "D - ToString",
			"correctAnswer": "C - Var"
		}
    },
	{
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 9 - Which of the following statements is correct about encapsulation?",
			"answerA": "A - Encapsulation is defined as the process of enclosing one \n or more items within a physical or logical package.",
			"answerB": "B - Encapsulation, in object oriented programming methodology, \n prevents access to implementation details.",
			"answerC": "C - Abstraction allows making relevant information visible and \n encapsulation enables a programmer to implement the desired level of abstraction.",
			"answerD": "D - All of the above.",
			"correctAnswer": "D - All of the above."
		}
    },
    {
		"Question": 
		{
			"question": "Q 10 - Which of the following is true about C# structures?",
			"answerA": "A - Structures can have methods, fields, indexers, \n properties, operator methods, and events.",
			"answerB": "B - Structures can have defined constructors, \n but not destructors.",
			"answerC": "C - You cannot define a default constructor for a structure. \n The default constructor is automatically defined and cannot be changed.",
			"answerD": "D - All of the above.",
			"correctAnswer": "D - All of the above."
		}
    }
]